I can feel their struggles,
but they have the words
in their head, but they
just can't say it. Yeah.
That's what makes me— Do
you remember what that felt
like? It felt like a
ball stuck in your throat.
Doesn't it get frustrating? Yeah,
it does get frustrating after
a while.
Well, you're lucky because you
got language, but there are
kids at your age that
still can't speak.
Do I have autism still?
Do you feel like you
still have autism? Yeah, sometimes
I do, but sometimes I
don't. What do you mean?
When do— I act a
little crazy. Sometimes when I
start to cry and feel
sensitive, that's when I feel
like I have autism. What
about friendship?
Yeah, that kind of feels
like I have autism too.
When I act cool around
friends, that moment I don't
seem to really have it.
But do you sometimes feel
like you don't have friends
because you have autism? Yeah.
You do? Yeah, sometimes I
see people that don't like
me sometimes because I have
autism. Right. When you were
little, you were really having
a hard time connecting and
making friends. They didn't understand
who you were.
Right? Yeah. What did they
ask you to say? I
asked you in the booty
hall. Are you kidding me?
You had boys that were
sending you up to girls
saying disgusting things. They make
me go in the girls'
bathroom. I did to
make friends. Anytime you have
someone that doesn't really understand
you, they're not going to
really know how to love
you because they don't know
who you are. I don't
want you to feel sad
about not having 25, 30
friends because you only really
need one or two good
friends, right? Yeah. Mom has
Auntie Terry. I have Wonder.
You have Wonder. You always
look tall for me. Would
Wonder ever put you in
a bad position where you
were either in harm's way
or you did something inappropriate?
He would never do that.
No. That's a real friend.
That is how you judge
who is your friend, who
has your back, who's looking
out for you.